[Music]
what is critical illness Insurance
simply put we'd all like to imagine a
future with perfect health but the right
time to plan for the unexpected is when
you're healthy why because once you
become ill your options might be limited
critical illness insurance is designed
to help you pay costs that may be
associated with certain life altering
illnesses it provides additional funds
if you become seriously ill this way you
can focus on your health and not your
finances how does critical illness
insurance work let's say you're
diagnosed with and survive one of the
illnesses covered as defined by your
insurance policy in such a case you'll
receive a one-time lumpsum cash payment
you can then use that money any way you
wish do you need critical illness
insurance so ask yourself do your other
insurance policies like life group
health or disability plans offer enough
coverage would your retirement goals
still be met if you had to take out say
$50,000 for expenses related to a
medical condition can you afford to take
on the costs associated with being
seriously ill this includes things like
loss of income travel to and from
treatment and home care
costs how can critical illness Insurance
help you it can help with those
additional costs that come up chances
are you know someone who's been affected
by serious health issues critical
illness insurance will provide you with
the Peace of Mind of knowing your
financially protected in case it happens
to you and it'll allow you to focus 100%
on your own recovery for more tips and
tools visit sunlife.ca
[Music]